<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Matt Bird - Software Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Matt Bird - Software Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Capture The Flag AI</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/ctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two teams of AI battle it out in a game of capture the flag against one another. These AI are built using a mix of decision trees and state machines to give them realistic and human like behaviors allowing for an immersive and challenging single player experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave Function Collapse Demo</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/wfc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My implementation of the physics-based wave function collapse algorithm. This tool can create automated and random 2D game levels, based on a pre-determined tile set given by any user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Terrain Generator</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/terraintool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/terraintool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An editor tool built in Unity Engine, designed to allow developers to effortlessly create custom and endlessly generating terrain systems for their games.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypersomnia</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/hypersomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/hypersomnia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An indie horror game created and published by me and a small team of junior programmers over a period of 2 months. Through out the duration of this project I was the lead AI programmer, managing a small team. Our responsibilities included creating the behaviors for the various adversaries faced throughout the game, alongside the implementation of other general gameplay programming tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iskandar - The Spear of Truth</title>
      <link>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/iskandar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:50:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mattbird.dev/portfolio/iskandar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An exploration/puzzle game created and published by me and a small group of junior programmers and designers. My main role in this project was programming the various boss encounters, a large majority of the game’s adversaries and implementation of general gameplay features.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
